Leon Davies

Web Design And Development

Contact

Address

Christchurch, CAN, 8024

Phone

027 484 8223

E-mail

leondavies1997@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/leon-davies-2805b9169/

Skills

Time Management

Excellent

Enthusiasm

Excellent

Communication

Excellen

Teamwork

Excellent

From an early age I discovered I loved fixing, upgrading and tinkering around with things, such as cars and more specifically computers.

I've always had a passion for computers and how they work which led me into studying computer science after high school. As much as I loved studying computer science after a year and a half I realized I wanted to combine my problem solving mindset with my creative side and use the skills I've learnt from University and swap over to a Diploma in Web Design and Development at Ara | Te Pūkenga Institute of Skills & Technology.

Throughout my work experience I have developed a high level of customer service which displays my understanding of patience and empathy.

I am really excited to start my career in the I.T industry and am even more excited to learn and further progress my skills and knowledge knowing I am ready to take on any challenge that may present itself.

Work History

2022-01 -Current

Community Support / Moderator

Blockmasons NFT, Christchurch, CAN

- Responding to help tickets
- Assigning roles to the appropriate users
- Setting up different language channels for non-English speakers
- Giving members general updates on the project so far
- Helped grow the project which now has 2100 members on discord

2021-04 -2022-07

Drive Through Customer Service

Mitre 10 Mega, Christchurch, CAN

- Giving customers product knowledge
- Providing excellent customer service
- Developing relationships and trust with customers and colleagues
- Handling orders and inquires over phone
- Cutting timber to specific dimensions

2016-02 -2016-09

Worksite Health and Safety

Jamon, Christchurch, CAN

- Educating workers on site of potential risks and hazards that may occur
- Knowledge of the appropriate safety plans on each site
- Monitoring of continual risks

Education

2021-06 - Diploma Level 5: Web Design And Development

Ara | Te Pūkenga – New Zealand Institute of Skills - Christchurch, CAN

2010-11 - High School Diploma

Burnside Highschool - Christchurch, CAN

NCEA 1

NCEA 2 Endorsed NCEA 3 Endorsed

Interests

2015-11

Learning new skills and putting myself out of my

comfort zone

Football

Cricket

Squash

Video games